A Guide to the Social Movements Collection, ca. 1959-1989, 2000, and n.d.
Special Collections, University of Virginia Library
- Series I: Topical Files
  - Southern Student Organizing Committee: University of Virginia Chapter - announcements, miscellaneous 1966-1968, n.d. (Box-folder 13:16)
  - Southern Student Organizing Committee: University of Virginia Chapter - Newsletters 1969 (Box-folder 13:17)
  - Soviet Jewry Research Bureau: National Conference on Soviet Jewry n.d. (Box-folder 14:1)
  - Spartacist League n.d. (Box-folder 14:2)
  - Steve Squire Defense Fund 1972-1977, n.d. (Box-folder 14:3)
  - Stop ERA n.d. (Box-folder 14:4)
  - Stop Hyde n.d. (Box-folder 14:5)
  - Stop the Pentagon 1982-1983, n.d. (Box-folder 14:6)
  - Stop the War Phone Book n.d. (Box-folder 14:7)
  - Student Mobilization Committee to End the War in Vietnam 1970, n.d. (Box-folder 14:8)
  - Students for a Democratic Society: Miscellaneous n.d. (Box-folder 14:9)
  - Students for a Democratic Society: Newsletters 1964-1968, n.d. (Box-folder 14:10)
  - Students for a Democratic Society: Publications - Civil Rights and Community Organization 1963-1969, n.d. (Box-folder 14:11)
  - Students for a Democratic Society: Publications - Economics 1963-1969, n.d. (Box-folder 14:12)
  - Students for a Democratic Society: Publications - Foreign Affairs 1962-1968, n.d. (Box-folder 14:13)
  - Students for a Democratic Society: Publications - Goldwater n.d. (Box-folder 14:14)
  - Students for a Democratic Society: Publications - Miscellaneous 1963-1968, n.d. (Box-folder 14:15)
  - Students for a Democratic Society: Publications - Students and Universities 1964-1968, n.d. (Box-folder 14:16)
  - Students for a Democratic Society: Publications - Vietnam 1963-1968, n.d. (Box-folder 14:17)
  - Students for a Democratic Society: University of Virginia n.d. (Box-folder 14:18)
  - Students for a Libertarian Society n.d. (Box-folder 15:1)
  - Support Committee to Send Legal-Medical Team of International Observers to Iran 1977 (Box-folder 15:2)
  - Susan Saxe Defense Committee 1975, n.d. (Box-folder 15:3)
  - TAP, the newsletter for the Phone Phreaks n.d. (Box-folder 15:4)
  - Target America: CIA Domestic Surveillance n.d. (Box-folder 15:5)
  - TECNICA: Technical Volunteers to Nicaragua 1987-1988, n.d. (Box-folder 15:6)
  - Three Mile Island Legal Fund n.d. (Box-folder 15:7)
  - The Thunderbolt, Inc. n.d. (Box-folder 15:8)
  - Tikkun Magazine n.d. (Box-folder 15:9)
  - Tom Daschle for United States Senate 1985-1986 (Box-folder 15:10)
  - Transarmament Network n.d. (Box-folder 15:11)
  - Twentieth Anniversary Mobilization 1983 (Box-folder 15:12)
  - Undo 1970, n.d. (Box-folder 15:13)
  - Union of Concerned Scientists 1987, n.d. (Box-folder 15:14)
  - Union of Councils for Soviet Jews n.d. (Box-folder 15:15)
  - Union of Democratic Thais n.d. (Box-folder 15:16)
  - Union Women's Alliance to Gain Equality (Union WAGE) n.d. (Box-folder 15:17)
  - United Electrical, Radio and Machine Workers of America (UE 124): Waynesboro, Virginia n.d. (Box-folder 15:18)
  - United Farm Workers n.d. (Box-folder 15:19)
  - United Food and Commercial Workers Union n.d. (Box-folder 15:20)
  - United Irish Societies n.d. (Box-folder 15:21)
  - United States-China Peoples Friendship Association of New York n.d. (Box-folder 15:22)
  - United States Committee in Solidarity with the People of El Salvador (CISPES) 1982-1986, n.d. (Box-folder 15:23)
  - United States Committee to Aid the National Liberation Front of South Vietnam n.d. (Box-folder 15:24)
  - United States Labor Party n.d. (Box-folder 15:25)
  - United States Out of Central America: A Project of the Latin America Resource Center and Clearinghouse n.d. (Box-folder 15:26)
  - United States Out of El Salvador n.d. (Box-folder 15:27)
  - United States Out of Lebanon Campaign n.d. (Box-folder 15:28)
  - Unity Resource 1981 (Box-folder 15:29)
  - University of Virginia 1968-1981 (Box-folder 15:30)
  - University of Virginia: Alumni Fund 1970 (Box-folder 15:31)
  - University of Virginia: American Friends of Free Palestine n.d. (Box-folder 15:32)
  - University of Virginia: Black Students for Freedom 1971 (Box-folder 15:33)
  - University of Virginia: Boycott Spiro Agnew Speech n.d. (Box-folder 15:34)
  - University of Virginia: CIA Protests 1975-1977 (Box-folder 15:35)
  - University of Virginia: Department of Government and Foreign Affairs 1970 (Box-folder 15:36)
  - University of Virginia: Fusion Club n.d. (Box-folder 15:37)
  - University of Virginia: General Ky Speech 1975 (Box-folder 15:38)
  - University of Virginia: Honor Committee 1959, n.d. (Box-folder 15:39)
  - University of Virginia: Labor Party Club n.d. (Box-folder 15:40)
  - University of Virginia: Library System 1983 (Box-folder 15:41)
  - University of Virginia: Madison Hall n.d. (Box-folder 15:42)
  - University of Virginia: May 1970 Strike - Arrest and Assault Information 1970 (Box-folder 16:1)
  - University of Virginia: May 1970 Strike - Candidates and Election Information 1970 (Box-folder 16:2)
  - University of Virginia: May 1970 Strike - Clippings 1970 (Box-folder 16:3)
  - University of Virginia: May 1970 Strike - Committees and Logistics 1970 (Box-folder 16:4)
  - University of Virginia: May 1970 Strike - Editorials 1970 (Box-folder 16:5)
  - University of Virginia: May 1970 Strike - Graduation 1970 (Box-folder 16:6)
  - University of Virginia: May 1970 Strike - Legislative Action 1970 (Box-folder 16:7)
  - University of Virginia: May 1970 Strike - Letters to Parents and Alumni 1970 (Box-folder 16:8)
  - University of Virginia: May 1970 Strike - Liberation Classes 1970 (Box-folder 16:9)
  - University of Virginia: May 1970 Strike - Mansfield Amendment 1970 (Box-folder 16:10)
  - University of Virginia: May 1970 Strike - McGovern-Hatfield Amendment 1970 (Box-folder 16:11)
  - University of Virginia: May 1970 Strike - Miscellaneous Correspondence and Notes 1970 (Box-folder 16:12)
  - University of Virginia: May 1970 Strike - Posters 1970 (Box-folder 16:13)
  - University of Virginia: May 1970 Strike - President Shannon Correspondence 1970 (Box-folder 16:14)
  - University of Virginia: May 1970 Strike - Raleigh Tavern Convention 1970 (Box-folder 16:15)
  - University of Virginia: May 1970 Strike - Schedules and Events 1970 (Box-folder 16:16)
  - University of Virginia: May 1970 Strike - Semester Grading and Scheduling 1970 (Box-folder 16:17)
  - University of Virginia: May 1970 Strike - Speeches 1970 (Box-folder 16:18)
  - University of Virginia: May 1970 Strike - Statements and Demands 1970 (Box-folder 16:19)
  - University of Virginia: May 1970 Strike - Student Council 1970 (Box-folder 16:20)
  - University of Virginia: May 1970 Strike - A Study of Protest 1978 (Box-folder 16:21)
  - University of Virginia: May 1970 Strike - A Study of Protest: Correspondence 1970 (Box-folder 16:22)
  - University of Virginia: May 1970 Strike - Veterans for Peace 1970 (Box-folder 16:23)
  - University of Virginia: May 1970 Strike - Vietnam War Information 1970 (Box-folder 16:24)
  - University of Virginia: May 1970 Strike - Young Americans for Freedom, Anti-Strike Groups 1970 (Box-folder 16:25)
  - University of Virginia: Meet the Senators Rally n.d. (Box-folder 17:1)
  - University of Virginia: Office of African-American Affairs 1984 (Box-folder 17:2)
  - University of Virginia: Personnel Office 1971 (Box-folder 17:3)
  - University of Virginia: Police Surveillance 1975 (Box-folder 17:4)
  - University of Virginia: Radical Student Union n.d. (Box-folder 17:5)
  - University of Virginia: Radical Student Union: Dow Chemical Company Protests n.d. (Box-folder 17:6)
  - University of Virginia: The Sally Hemings: Notes n.d. (Box-folder 17:7)
  - University of Virginia: Society of Articulate Thugs n.d. (Box-folder 17:8)
  - University of Virginia: Strike Committee 1970 (Box-folder 17:9)
  - University of Virginia: Student Appropriations and Allocations n.d. (Box-folder 17:10)
  - University of Virginia: Student Coalition (Box-folder 17:11)
  - University of Virginia: Student Council: Miscellaneous 1968-1975 (Box-folder 17:12)
  - University of Virginia: Student Council: Report: Employment Committee 1969 (Box-folder 17:13)
  - University of Virginia: Student Council: Report: Student Attitudes and Opinions 1971 (Box-folder 17:14)
  - University of Virginia: Students for a Free Society n.d. (Box-folder 17:15)
  - University of Virginia: The Ten Days n.d. (Box-folder 17:16)
  - University of Virginia: Union of University Students n.d. (Box-folder 17:17)
  - University of Virginia: University Committee for a Responsible Peace in Vietnam n.d. (Box-folder 17:18)
  - University of Virginia: University Union 1975 (Box-folder 17:19)
  - University of Virginia: Veterans of Future Wars n.d. (Box-folder 17:20)
  - University of Virginia: Vietnam Moratorium Committee n.d. (Box-folder 17:21)
  - University of Virginia: Virginia Council on Human Relations 1968-1969, n.d. (Box-folder 17:22)
  - University of Virginia: Young Americans for Freedom n.d. (Box-folder 17:23)
  - University of Virginia: Young Democrats 1964 (Box-folder 17:24)
  - University of Virginia: Youth Coalition Against Abortion 1973, n.d. (Box-folder 17:25)
  - University Review n.d. (Box-folder 17:26)
  - Upper Valley Vietnam Group n.d. (Box-folder 17:27)
  - Upstate Resistance 1982-1985 (Box-folder 17:28)
  - Veterans Education Project n.d. (Box-folder 17:29)
  - Veterans Fast-For-Life n.d. (Box-folder 17:30)
  - Veterans for Peace in Vietnam n.d. (Box-folder 17:31)
  - Vicki Gabriner Defense Fund 1978 (Box-folder 17:32)
  - Video Display Terminals 1983 (Box-folder 17:33)
  - Vietnam Summer: Richmond, Virginia 1967 (Box-folder 17:34)
  - Vietnam Trial Support Committee 1978, n.d. (Box-folder 17:35)
  - Vietnam Veterans Against the War 1974 (Box-folder 17:36)
  - Virginia Action n.d. (Box-folder 17:37)
  - Virginia Association of Railway Patrons 1985-1986, n.d. (Box-folder 17:38)
  - Virginia Citizens Party 1981 (Box-folder 17:39)
  - Virginia College Students Opposed to the 21 Law 1983 (Box-folder 17:40)
  - Virginia ERA Ratification Council 1975-1978 (Box-folder 17:41)
  - Virginia Governmental Employees Association, Inc. (VGEA) 1959, n.d. (Box-folder 17:42)
  - Virginia Interfaith Action Community 1968 (Box-folder 17:43)
  - Virginia Liberation Party n.d. (Box-folder 17:44)
  - Virginia Mobilization Committee to End the War in Vietnam n.d. (Box-folder 17:45)
  - Virginia Organization to Keep Abortion Legal (VOKAL) 1980-1984, n.d. (Box-folder 17:46)
  - Virginia Peace and Freedom Party n.d. (Box-folder 17:47)
  - Virginia Public Interest Research Group (VaPIRG) n.d. (Box-folder 17:48)
  - Virginia Renewable Energy Lobby 1980 (Box-folder 17:49)
  - Virginia Research Institute n.d. (Box-folder 17:50)
  - Virginia Research Project 1971 (Box-folder 17:51)
  - Virginia Society for Human Life 1983 (Box-folder 17:52)
  - Virginia Sunshine Alliance 1979, n.d. (Box-folder 17:53)
  - Virginia Veterans for Peace 1970, n.d. (Box-folder 17:54)
  - The Virginia Weekly 1969, n.d. (Box-folder 17:55)
  - Viva Inez 1976 (Box-folder 17:56)
  - Wall Street Action-part of the Manhattan Project n.d. (Box-folder 18:1)
  - War Resisters League 1969-1983, n.d. (Box-folder 18:2)
  - War Resisters League: 1972 Peace Calendar 1972 (Box-folder 18:3)
  - War Tax Resistance 1970-1976, n.d. (Box-folder 18:4)
  - Washington Area Coalition Against Registration and the Draft n.d. (Box-folder 18:5)
  - Washington Area Committee Against Registration and the Draft n.d. (Box-folder 18:6)
  - Washington Area Resistance n.d. (Box-folder 18:7)
  - Washington Office on Africa 1984, n.d. (Box-folder 18:8)
  - The Washington Peace Center n.d. (Box-folder 18:9)
  - Washington Project for the Arts 1987 (Box-folder 18:10)
  - The Washington School: A Project of the Institute for Policy Studies 1987-1988 (Box-folder 18:11)
  - Weather Underground 1970-1977, n.d. (Box-folder 18:12)
  - Weather Underground: Clippings 1970-1982, n.d. (Box-folder 18:13)
  - Westchester Coalition for Legal Abortion n.d. (Box-folder 18:14)
  - Western Solidarity 1986, n.d. (Box-folder 18:15)
  - White House Daily Meeting 1973 (Box-folder 18:16)
  - Whole Life Times n.d. (Box-folder 18:17)
  - Williams Peacemakers Defense Fund n.d. (Box-folder 18:18)
  - Win Magazine n.d. (Box-folder 18:19)
  - Women Against Daddy Warbucks: New York Women's Draft Board n.d. (Box-folder 18:20)
  - Women Free Women In Prison n.d. (Box-folder 18:21)
  - Women's Campaign Fund 1984-1988 (Box-folder 18:22)
  - Women's Health Center of Charlottesville 1981-1986, n.d. (Box-folder 18:23)
  - Women's History Research Lobby 1969-1971, n.d. (Box-folder 18:24)
  - Women's International League for Peace and Freedom 1979-1984, n.d. (Box-folder 18:25)
  - Women's Liberation ZAP Action Brigade 1981 (Box-folder 18:26)
  - Women's Middle East Committee to Support the Palestinians n.d. (Box-folder 18:27)
  - Women's Pentagon Action n.d. (Box-folder 18:28)
  - Workers World Party 1980 (Box-folder 18:29)
  - Working/Women's Institute 1984 (Box-folder 18:30)
  - World Peace Tax Fund n.d. (Box-folder 18:31)
  - Wounded Knee Legal Defense/Offense Committee 1973-1977 (Box-folder 18:32)
  - Yippie: Youth International Party 1982, n.d. (Box-folder 18:33)
  - Yippie: Abbie Hoffman 1975-1979, n.d. (Box-folder 18:34)
  - Yipster Times/Overthrow n.d. (Box-folder 18:35)
  - Young Americans for Freedom n.d. (Box-folder 18:36)
  - Young National Socialist Corps n.d. (Box-folder 18:37)
  - Youth Against War and Fascism 1972-1973, n.d. (Box-folder 18:38)
  - Youth Coalition, May Day Collective n.d. (Box-folder 18:39)
- Series II: Memorabilia
  - Memorabilia: Armband n.d. (Box-folder 19:1)
  - Memorabilia: Bracelet: Amnesty for Dick Bucklin n.d. (Box-folder 19:2)
  - Memorabilia: Buttons: Anarchy n.d. (Box-folder 19:3)
  - Memorabilia: Buttons: Black Panthers n.d. (Box-folder 19:4)
  - Memorabilia: Buttons: Charlottesville n.d. (Box-folder 19:5)
  - Memorabilia: Buttons: Defense Funds, miscellaneous n.d. (Box-folder 19:6)
  - Memorabilia: Buttons: Draft n.d. (Box-folder 19:7)
  - Memorabilia: Buttons: Elections, Candidates 1976-1984, n.d. (Box-folder 19:8)
  - Memorabilia: Buttons: IRA n.d. (Box-folder 19:9)
  - Memorabilia: Buttons: Latin America, International Affairs n.d. (Box-folder 19:10)
  - Memorabilia: Buttons: Marches, Miscellaneous 1976-1981, n.d. (Box-folder 19:11)
  - Memorabilia: Buttons: Miscellaneous n.d. (Box-folder 19:12)
  - Memorabilia: Buttons: Nixon n.d. (Box-folder 19:13)
  - Memorabilia: Buttons: Nuclear War and Power 1980, n.d. (Box-folder 19:14)
  - Memorabilia: Buttons: Palestine n.d. (Box-folder 19:15)
  - Memorabilia: Buttons: Peace n.d. (Box-folder 19:16)
  - Memorabilia: Buttons: Pro-Choice Abortion 1986, n.d. (Box-folder 19:17)
  - Memorabilia: Buttons: South Africa n.d. (Box-folder 19:18)
  - Memorabilia: Buttons: Students for a Democratic Society n.d. (Box-folder 19:19)
  - Memorabilia: Buttons: Taxes, War Taxes n.d. (Box-folder 19:20)
  - Memorabilia: Buttons: Unions and Farm Boycotts n.d. (Box-folder 19:21)
  - Memorabilia: Buttons: Vietnam n.d. (Box-folder 19:22)
  - Memorabilia: Buttons: Women's Issues n.d. (Box-folder 19:23)
  - Memorabilia: Buttons: Yippie 1976-1977, n.d. (Box-folder 19:24)
  - Memorabilia: Cover Art by Aaron Fagen [1972]
    concerning University Student Protests, particularly Students for a Democratic Society, pasted on a wooden board
  - Memorabilia: Keychain: Peace for El Salvador n.d. (Box-folder 19:25)
  - Memorabilia: Stickers: Miscellaneous n.d. (Box-folder 19:26)
  - Memorabilia: Stickers: Nixon n.d. (Box-folder 19:27)
  - Memorabilia: Stickers: No Nukes 1977, n.d. (Box-folder 19:28)
  - Memorabilia: Stickers: Palestine n.d. (Box-folder 19:29)
- Series III: Personal Papers
  - Charlie Finn Personal: Correspondence - Contribution Letters 1982-1988 (Box-folder 20:1)
  - Charlie Finn Personal: Correspondence - Letters to Politicians and Organizations 1970-1988 (Box-folder 20:2)
  - Charlie Finn Personal: Correspondence: Letters to the Editor 1973-1987, n.d. (Box-folder 20:3)
  - Charlie Finn Personal: Correspondence: Official 1975-1976, n.d. (Box-folder 20:4)
  - Charlie Finn Personal: Correspondence: Personal 1968-1987, n.d. (Box-folder 20:5)
  - Charlie Finn Personal: Court Orders 1971 (Box-folder 20:6)
  - Charlie Finn Personal: Events 1973-1985, n.d. (Box-folder 20:7)
  - Charlie Finn Personal: Miscellaneous 1987, n.d. (Box-folder 20:8)
  - Charlie Finn Personal: Notes: Miscellaneous n.d. (Box-folder 20:9)
  - Charlie Finn Personal: PL480 1971-1973, n.d. (Box-folder 20:10)
  - Charlie Finn Personal: Social Movements Collection 1976-1980, n.d. (Box-folder 20:11)
  - Charlie Finn Personal: University of Virginia 1970-1988 (Box-folder 20:12)
  - Charlie Finn Personal: University of Virginia Library 1971-1980 (Box-folder 20:13)
  - Charlie Finn Personal: Writings n.d. (Box-folder 20:14)